<resources xmlns:xsl="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">MMIS_ver2</string>
    <string name="title_activity_splash">MMIS_ver2</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_create_order">Create Order</string>
    <string name="action_share">Share</string>
    <string name="title">MMIS</string>

    <string-array name="titles">
        <item>Home</item>
        <item>AFRES</item>
        <item>PRIME</item>
        <item>Traffic Management System</item>
        <item>Implementation of MIS</item>
        <item>Fuel Accounting System</item>
        <item>Web Designing</item>
        <item>Extra</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="open_drawer">Open drawer</string>
    <string name="close_drawer">Close drawer</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment"></string>

    <string name="write">\n
      <center> <b> MMIS</b><i> (Materials Management Information System): </i> </center> \n\n

        <p>  \t Materials Management Information System was developed at Central Railway in 1998 initially for COS
            office, Stores A/c. office and five major depots of the C.Rly viz. CRD, PR, MTN, JHS and VVH. Since
            then, the system has undergone several customization and is now successfully implemented on all Stores
            Depot, Divisions &amp; Stores finance branch. The field units (Depots &amp; Divisions) are depots in
            Central Railway, 14 depots are connected online to the Centralized connected to server at Hqtrs
            through railnet.</p>\n\n

         <p>   With implementation of MMIS, the quality of work and output has improved, flow of information is
            very quick. There has been transparency in the working and as per CVC guidelines high value
            purchase, single tender purchase, sales information etc. has been posted on the net. All this
            has been possible because of successful implementation of MMIS.</p>\n\n

        The details of all modules implemented under MMIS as below:\n\n

       <p>(a)<b>Purchase Module</b>: The entire process of procurement i.e. from Initiation of Demand to release of
            purchase order and post purchase activities are fully computerized. This has resulted in
            saving of lead time of the procurement cycle and also improve availability of the items to
            the internal users. The information of the system is available on Intranet for managerial
            decisions. </p>\n\n

        <p>(b)<b>Finance Module</b>: Implemented at Stores A/c. in HQ. Bill passing activities, payments and Stores
            Monthly Summaries are being generated through MMIS.</p>\n\n

        <p>(c)<b>Depot Module</b>: Implemented in the depots. Sub modules are Ledger Section, Yard, Transaction Module,
            Receiving Section,  Fabrication, Returned Stores, etc. Here again the entire depot working
            is computerized and data is transferred to and fro depot electronically.</p>\n\n

        <p>(d)<b>Uniform Module</b>: This module facilitated for monitoring of uniform supply to
            the railway employees.</p>\n\n

        <p>(e)<b>Sales Module</b>: This module for monitoring of sale activity (disposal of
            scrap) of the railway.</p>\n\n

        <p>(f)<b>LP Module</b>: This module designed, developed and implemented in Divisions &amp;
            depot for petty purchase activities.</p>\n\n


        <p> Indentor and Vendor related information is also available on both Internet
            (www.cr.indianrailways.gov.in and on Intranet of the railway.\n The site contains static
            information viz. Vendor Guide, Indenters Guide, Information regarding Materials Management
            Department, SOPGEN etc. and dynamic information like Stock Position, Non-Stock Demand
            Information, Vendor Bill Position, Vendor Registration Status, Vendor Information, Auction
            Catalogue, Auction Program and various other reports for both Indenters and Vendors.</p>\n"
    </string>


    <string name="afres">
              \n <B> Advanced Finance and Railway Earning And Expenditure System (AFRES)</B>\n

<p>AFRES is an integrated system that covers the working of the accounts office at the zone
level and at the division level. The system handles payments made by the Railways, bookkeeping
 and accounting of railway earnings apart from regular finance and accounts functions. A number
 of associated activities are also covered. It covers the PF, Pension, Internal Check, Suspense, Book,
  Cash and Pay and Traffic modules.</p>
       \n The followings are modules of AFRES:\n


(a) PF.\n
(b) Pension Module.\n
(c) Internal Check.\n
(d) Books Module.\n
(e) Suspense Module.\n
(f) Pay Module.\n
(g) Cash Module.\n
(h) Traffic Module.\n
(i) Bank Guarantee Module\n
(j) New Pension Scheme Module\n
(k) Remittance in Bank Module.\n

   </string>

    <string name="prime">
        \n
        <b>Payroll and Related Independent Module (PRIME)</b>:\n\n
        <p>This module covers most of the activities of the working of branch. The application was developed
        by the same vendor under guidance of Southern Railway and now being adopted by all other railways.\n
        </p>
        The main modules under this package are:\n\n

    Payroll for open line staff.\n
    Payroll for workshop staff.\n
    Leave modules.\n
    Income Tax Module.\n
    PLB.\n
    Supplementary Bill preparation.\n
    Career Events Modules.\n
    Welfare Module.\n
    Quarters Module.\n
    Pass Module\n
    Cadre (Book of Sanctions).\n
    Settlement."
    </string>


    <string name="traffic">\n \t
        <b><center>Traffic Management System \n</center></b><p>
        Traffic application is the oldest application introduced in Indian Railways
        computer system in 1967. It was running in Auto Coder language from 1967 to 1985. In 1986
        it was converted to COBOL. The followings are module of traffic management system:Traffic application is the oldest application introduced in Indian Railways
        computer system in 1967. It was running in Auto Coder language from 1967 to 1985. In 1986
        it was converted to COBOL.\n</p>

        Traffic application: The Traffic application broadly covers the following:\n

        a. Freight (General Goods, Coal, CONCOR)\n
        b. PCT (Passenger Classifications (manual), local/foreign)\n
        c. PRS (Passenger Reservation System)\n
        d. UTS (Unreserved Ticketing System)\n
        e. BPT/EFT Blank Paper Ticket/ Extended Fare Ticket)\n
        f.  Season (Computerized and Centralized)\n
        g. Military (Manual Warrant)\n
        h. Non-Military force/Military (PRS and Manual)\n
        i.  Card Vending Machine Ticket (CVM) (proposed).\n
        j.  Engine and EMU Operating Reports.\n
    </string>

    <string name="fuel">
        \n<b><center>Fuel Accounting System\n</center></b>
        <p>The Fuel Accounting System keeps track of the Accounts of High Speed Diesel
         (HSD) oil receipt &amp; issued to locos and other purpose. High Speed Diesel oil being a very
         sensitive item needs to be closely monitored as it is costly and its consumption is very high.\n</p>

       <p>This was processed in COBOL till 31.March 2007. Now it is switched over to ORACLE-D2K based (RDBMS)
           system.The migration from COBOL to ORACLE was done in-house by IT Center. The data entry of this
           application is being done by the users from fueling points itself through Railnet.</p>
    </string>

    <string name="web">
        \n<b><center>Web Designing\n</center></b>
       <p> IT Center has designed in-house website which covers information about
        IT Center, Training Programmes, Library, MMIS, MIS, Traffic etc. Various useful programs
         are developed for MMIS information Like Stock &amp; dues, consumption pattern, inventory,
         Purchases, vendor and is updated regularly. The website also provides useful downloads
         for the computers, telephone numbers of important services etc. Further additional useful
         information pages are continuously developed in-house and provided on website to make it more
          and more useful and user friendly.</p>
    </string>

    <string name="Mis">\n
        <b><center>Implementation of MIS\n</center></b>
        IT centre is also providing assistance to other department for implementation
         of following modules for internal use:\n

(a) <b>Electrical MIS (EMIS)</b>: Non-Traction Energy Management module for General Services customized
 Central Railway has been implemented and successfully utilized on all the divisions.\n

 Assets Management module for General Services customized by Central Railway has been implemented
 and successfully used on all the divisions.\n

(b)<b>S&amp;T MIS</b>: Application for Signaling and Telecom activities originally developed by Southern Railway
 has been successfully customized and replicated on all the divisions of C.Rly.\n

Integrated Zonal Database  of all the divisional S&amp;T MIS data of BB, BSL, NGP, PA and SUR divisions is
 deployed in centralized database server (Sun ? RISC) kept at BSL Division.
    </string>
</resources>
